All right, I'll cover all the regular schedule made in my mistake as a two, they mark 17, 20, 20, and you six.
I don't know if I can put on schedule personal appearances.
We have done three approval and presentation of the Propformation and Proclamation and Cliring
April 20, 26 as autism awareness and a push or acceptance month.
Motion group.
Sorry.
Delo golf.
Part.
Barnes.
A step.
Jones.
Part.
for that. For for a presentation from the Myana Area Economic Development Services, Mr.
Chan and Mr. Chan do on on Mr. Keesh's.
What's on your hair?
Please go and be sure.
Five minutes. Five minutes.
Five minutes.
presentation focuses primarily on some of the things we're doing in the city limits of
Miami, but we are doing some other things. This was kind of the rollout that we did.
There is a more detailed version of this presentation that I can share with you on a
individual basis if you'd like, but this is going to hit some of the highlights and I
think it's important because we fit the ground running. You know, several of us went to
the San Antonio in February for the ICSC Red River Show. I'm going to end this presentation.
I'm going to kind of update you an overall and where we are and the follow-up to some of
the connections that we made at that conference. But this is, I wanted you to see this
because this is going to help you better understand what retail strategies is doing for us.
In addition with our working side-by-side with us as well as the city, let's give that.
So here's kind of who retail strategies is and here's some of the things that they're focusing on.
So remember it's a three-year contract. So you're one, the focus is to begin to immerse themselves
in our community, get to know the local players that move our market, uncover opportunities and
stories that need to be told about our community and start connecting those opportunities
to the decision makers with those retailers that we're actively trying to recruit.
And we took a big step in doing that when we went to...
San Antonio.
Year two, we ramp up those efforts in conjunction with retail strategies.
We go a little bit deeper into understanding who we're targeting and what we expect when
those potential outcomes from those targets.
They'll continue to outreach the correct retail prospects, deepen those relationships,
and again, they will continue to up retail strategies continuously updates on everything
that they're doing.
In fact, this afternoon I was sharing with Tyler and the mayor, we use a special online platform
where we're constantly exchanging updates and emails and messages almost multiple times
a day.
And then by year three, that's when you historically start to see positive momentum.
Now, the good news is, based on what we've already been working on just to the last couple
of months, I don't think we have to wait for the third year to start seeing some of
those benefits.
We're actually seeing a lot of positive feedback right now.
So that's very encouraging and exciting.
But year three is when we start to see that success.
We build on what we do and year one and year two, get that foundation lay.
We see those businesses start coming in by year three, and then from that point on we can just
continue to grow from there.
So I'm going to go through this really quickly.
The city uses a program called Place or AI, you're still using that program, Tyler?
Yes, sir.
So you know how that works?
One of the things that's interesting about that, and I apologize for that graphic being a little
blurry, but that data gives us a good picture of how many people are coming into our community
and in our community that are going to our different retailers.
So you can't hardly tell, but so this is my humble Walmart here.
What's important about that is I know you can't see, and I apologize.
In our region, which includes the yo-show, both job and stores, Pineville, Missouri, Wetch City,
Nevada, Carthage, Pittsburgh, I know I'll excuse me, should need a Parsons bar that is for it.
Our Miami Walmart is third out of all of those stores in business on a daily basis.
Why is that important?
That's data that we can take and give to other potential retailers that want to know how things
are moving in my own local home, we can say, look, our Miami Walmart has over 900,000 visits a year.
I have to lose or me, lessen our back to back on that, so that's just Walmart, right?
So just take it as a little step further, here's the Miami.
Sonic, again, and that same region were third.
That's big.
That's important.
Look at this.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, look at it.
One over one million visits a year.
You take this with your Nokia phone or what?
No, I said it's their program, blah, blah.
Over one million visits a year to the Miami Sonic.
And so that's great data.
That's information that's very useful to prospective businesses.
And so here's a basic snapshot of our consumer trade area.
The average, depending on which program you look at, which data company you look at.
The median household income in Ottawa County is $50,000 per year.
Some show it a little lower than that.
I've seen a couple that haven't just a little bit higher like around $52.
That's a pretty good number.
I'd say on average, for Ottawa County anywhere from $48 to $52,000.
$52,000 a year isn't the average of what our average median household income is.
Current population, almost $29,000.
Number of households, $11,253, and the average age of our residents is just under 40.
So you look at our trade demographic area.
And this is kind of based on that data that I showed you earlier.
It's based on some of that wall-borne information.
It's based on some of that sonic information.
And other retailers in our community.
And within a three mile radius, five mile radius, and so forth,
you can see the current population.
This is a number I think most people lose side of.
This is daytime population.
So even though the population in Miami is roughly around 13,000,
during the daytime hours though, that number is closer to 17.5.
You extend that out to a five mile radius around the city of Miami.
That number of jobs, it's almost 19,000 daily in Miami.
So that's important.
Those are the kind of data that our retailers that we're trying to recruit or look at.
That's your restaurants, that's your retail outlets, your home improvement stores, things of that nature.
This is the kind of data that we're providing now to those retailers.
And so another big key to that's going to work
help us, especially retail strategies, and their work, is what's called pure analysis.
Pure analysis is where they take other communities in other areas that are close to us,
population wise.
If you look at these, this goes up to like 16,000.
It looks at what their daytime population numbers are, because that's important.
It looks at the median household income.
Now, this is just the city of Miami.
So the county is around 50, but just...
in the city of Miami, you're down to 44.
And then here is what the market is.
This is what the market supports.
So that's $160 million a year in Miami.
Why is that important when you look at, say,
Ripley, Tennessee, which has $13,000 people,
they're $231 million a year?
Well, if they're basically the same size we are,
and they have the same kind of makeup that we are,
what do they have in their community?
That's generating that extra revenue that we don't.
Because if a business is willing to be in that community,
when they only have 13 or 14,000 people,
why aren't they here in Miami or Oklahoma?
So you take that argument away where they say,
well, you don't meet all of our immigrants.
Well, we don't necessarily believe that.
We've got pretty close to the same population base.
We have the same kind of industry.
We have a lot of similarities.
You may have a college.
We've got a junior college.
We have all those things.
But you have, they have lows, or maybe a home deep up.
Maybe they have all these.
Why can't they be here?
That's what the Parenthalysis tells us.
So we'll go look in those communities and see
what they have that we don't,
and then we'll use this information to our benefit.
To try to help get them to take the closer look
at what we're doing here in Miami, Oklahoma.
Does that make sense?
Okay.
We went home.
Gap analysis.
I think I was here not to go and talk a little bit
about gap analysis, and that's those areas
where we're missing out on opportunities.
That's our residence going somewhere else to shop,
and spend their money somewhere else,
which drives their sales tax revenue,
which pays their street, pays their loan force,
and pays their fire for me, and not ours.
So when you look at these numbers,
this is kind of a snapshot of where we're missing the boat.
And where our greatest gaps are that we need to fill,
restaurants and bars, food and beverage stores,
about this one, building material, garden, supply stores,
think lows, think Home Depot, some of it's places like that.
That information is what's allowing us
to find two who our targets are.
Question.
So when we say we're going out and recruiting businesses,
we're going to use this data
that the gap analysis covers a lot more categories.
This is just a snapshot.
We're going to look for see where our biggest losses are
to other communities, and we're going to try to meet those needs
so we can keep those dollars here.
And so that's the priority list.
Now I think I told you last time that doesn't mean
if someone wants to come to town and they're not on our target list,
We're going to say, no, we don't want you.
That's the way we don't do that.
Mayor Park is very fond of saying we're open for business.
We don't turn any one away.
Someone will send best money dollars into our community.
We want to hear what they have to say.
And we want to help them in any way we can.
But yes, we have a very specific target list of businesses we want for sure.
And our community, we're aggressively going after those.
But everybody's welcome.
I'll show you how we understand the scale that's just for my own.
I could be knowledge in this.
So the bigger the bar is the less we needers at the opposite.
No, that means that's the greater opportunity.
Okay.
That makes sense.
This is money leaving my end.
Okay.
And these are the kind of reports.
So when we bring in a pop ice.
And people say, we didn't need pop ice.
We don't need more restaurants.
This tells you just the opposite.
Now I don't need pop ice.
We need more.
Because that's why we're driving a job on.
Because we don't have enough here.
And that's the the leaky.
We're trying to stop.
Because when you're a job and spending your dollars.
It's not helping my own.
And the thing I think to really focus on is.
It's not that we just need more restaurants.
Right?
What we need is variety and restaurants.
We all love hamburgers.
Right?
We all love pizza.
We all love Mexican food.
We love all those things.
And that's not to say if another one of you.
Those were to become.
If water, water, water to come to our.
I'd be the first one in life.
I mean, that's just me honest.
But the reality is when we're talking about targeted.
Retail businesses.
We're looking for variety.
What.
What do we not have.
In our restaurants.
That people believe in our community.
Whether it's.
Fast food restaurants.
Whether it's actual sit down dining restaurants.
Whatever the case may be.
We're.
We're those gaps.
And how do we still.
You know, Sam.
Sam.
Then we have the downtown Miami corridor, and then what we have the eastern corridor, which is right off the turn by.
And so, these are kind of examples of where we're focusing, where there's available property, or available vacant buildings.
And then you don't get to see it here, but then the full slide show that we did with retail strategies.
They broke it down even further, and they were actually for each one of our select sites.
They had a list of potential targets to go in that particular location.
But those are our three main corridors for development.
And so, what that does is they look at, they do a SWAT analysis for each one of those corridors.
And each one of those projected sites you all probably should be strengths, weaknesses, opportunities, threats.
If you've ever had to sit through leadership training or anything like that, you know what a SWAT analysis is.
And so, I'm not going to hit all these, but I'll talk about this one.
So, what are some of our strengths of major retailer anchors on the Northern corridor?
Well more.
US69 provides strong regional through traffic, as well as I-44.
And in entertainment, venues generate consistent visitor traffic that spills over into retail opportunities.
Weaknesses, our corridors don't naturally connect.
They do, by road, right?
But downtown kind of separates the Northern corridor from the eastern corridor.
So, there's a little bit of a flow issue there.
It's just the way we're laid out.
It's not a whole lot we can do about it.
It just presents some challenges that we need to deal with and try to overcome.
Opportunities, I-44, US69, a interchange.
And then, obviously, you need to determine how to get underdeveloped.
That's some of that changing.
Obviously, with the announcement of quick trip coming there on the corner.
Ground lease and purchase structures lower barriers to entry for franchises.
So, not everything has to be sold out, right?
Some companies, and we talked to some while we were in San Antonio, that are not opposed to leasing ground,
whether it's from individuals or from our tribal partners.
As you know, quick trip is a brown lease to give you an example of what we're talking about.
And then, well-position sites across the market.
We do have a number of sites that are primed for development.
If we get the right development procedure to deal with those things.
Some of the threats, Dublin, being where they are and what they have available in Dublin,
sucks some of that money out of our community on a regular basis.
Natural, national franchise brands increasingly favored larger MSAs, which is larger communities.
That have a bigger population based, a higher average home meeting, home income.
And so, you know,
Those are threats to some of the things we do with some companies, not all, but with some.
And then of course, one of the biggest things that's affecting us in a lot of areas, not just in retail development,
but in housing development and everything else.
And that's the rising cost of construction in this country today.
And so what retail strategies they went through, they listed a bunch of different sites that they consider like their top five.
They go through and they give you some stress and weaknesses for each one of those.
And this basically just breaking down that overall SWAT analysis into specific sites.
I'm not going to go into all those sites and the reason is, I don't want to tip anybody's hand over.
We're trying to develop just yet.
That always affects the price.
So you have to be careful.
I also took out the slides that show the businesses that we were targeting for those each one of those specific things.
Because we didn't want to give that information because if you put it on a slide, community sees that and then they, oh, we're getting company XYZ.
That doesn't work that way.
That just means they're a target and we're trying to get company XYZ.
So some key results.
So here's the objective, proper assessment of the Miami-Drader market, come back with property owners and their agents for identified opportunities.
And results need a first success.
We want to identify the top opportunities for retailers here.
We want to perform outreach for top opportunities in the market.
And we want to provide accurate and timely reporting, not just to maids because we have the contract.
But to the city, to our tribal partners.
Because in the end we're all partners and we're all in this together.
I can't do it without the city.
I can't do it without our tribal partners.
It's, you know, we're all in it together.
So that being said, I'm going to stop there.
If you have any other questions about this, I'm happy to answer them.
Otherwise, I'll just kind of give you a quick update on where we are and I'll follow up to ICSC.
That's a good question for you in a moment.
Okay.
So we did go to San Antonio in February.
And it was a very productive trip.
There were six of us that went.
We had a good time.
They climbed a lot into a day and a half.
But the beauty of that is we made some amazing contacts.
Tyler and bless.
I think we'll share that with you as well.
Right after that, we kind of reassessed and kind of took a,
Inventory of who we visited with, who were the really strong possibilities, the good leads,
Prioritized those and then we started reaching out to those companies.
I've been reaching out to them.
I think Tyler has reached out to some and then retail strategies has reached out to some as well.
And then the beauty of that is as we reach out to these companies and they respond.
We upload all that information to retail strategies.
So they know every conversation we're having with every potential retailer.
So.
that we all are operating with the same information in real time.
But the beauty is, we are now seeing responses to that, and some very encouraging responses
from a lot of different types of businesses, restaurants, a couple retail outlets, and
really just is important, developers, key developers.
And so we met the afternoon, Mayor Parker and Tyler myself to Kish was in there as well.
Just to kind of get everybody up to speed on what the conversations we've been having.
And these retailers are now reaching back out to us and asking for very specific site location
information, whether there's existing buildings, if not, they're looking for size, acreage,
pricing, that's encouraging because, six months ago, we weren't getting any of that.
But now, because we've gone down there and we've had those meetings, we've met face
to face with them, they know who we are, Mayor Parker was out passing out as a challenge
coins that you have, those mirrors, and people weren't eating that up.
I mean, they love it.
And so we're going to get a great opportunity to go out and go out and point it.
But it's little things like that.
People remember.
And so when I'm sending out emails, I, to one particular company, I say, I'll invite
the way the mayor hopes you enjoyed your challenge coin that he gave you at the show and they
were spawned back saying, I remember that.
I still have that.
That was great.
We were opening doors that we couldn't open before because of that.
And because of our partnership with retail strategies, we were able, it's odd that we had
to go all the way to San Antonio to do that.
But one of the big developers that we met down there is currently based on a local home
city.
But he went to NEO.
And so that was exciting.
We had great conversations with him.
He's asked for specific information from us on some certain sites so that he can get back
with his team so that they can determine how they can best help us.
And so we are a leaps and bounds ahead of where we were six months ago, a year ago.
And it's exciting, it's encouraging.
And we don't think we're going to have to wait the standard three years to see some results.
We think we're going to see some things happening before then.
And once we get that ball rolling, it's going to feed other development.
It's going to feed other companies wanting to come and be a part of what's happening here and keep
our tax dollars, our sales tax dollars, here, not job.
Any questions?
I kept it as short as I could.
You did awesome.
Okay.
I'll take you back on a little bit about that.
I see SC.
Of course it was first on Tyler and I never went.
It didn't really know to expect.
But going to those.
Definitely made an impact to put my mind on the map with people that we've never been on the map with before
because we were there. We were networking
You know, Tyler Scott and introvert, but he was all always playing. He was networking. He was talking to people and
When you get down on that's what you gotta do. You gotta get out. You gotta talk to them
The challenge coins that turned to gave me. Yeah, I took something with me and didn't know and every time I had one to someone
And I didn't hand them to just anyone. He was people we really had a good conversation with that we really built a relationship with and
When I gave it to them
They look on their face was
Wow, you know because you can't business cards all day and they stick with it all like I do everybody get them in there
And I look at them later, but that challenge coin we saw one of the guys the next day and he goes hey
You're the guy. He's the challenge coin. So he remembered me because of that coin
We had another good conversation and he's one of them that's reached out and is
We feel probably I feel more confident in that one than any of them at this point that they'll be here, but
There's several good things
Coming from my am I and I wish I could tell you what they are, but I can't
She had it with hurt me
But it's exciting because the work's paying off and I think I don't want anybody to think
And it's all you know alcohol and dancing girls and everything else when we go to these shows
I mean, we're actually a bit of working
But I thought the best compliment we have was from your wife when we were at the reception
And we said okay guys time to work the room and
She's like you'll just jumped up and y'all were gone and y'all were everywhere y'all were talking to everybody
You know speaking with everybody because it was amazing that she said I'd never seen that before
Yeah, I've been married my wife for 35 years
We were walking back from the reception of the hotel and she looked at me. She said I was really impressed
That said it only took me 35 years to hear you say I impressed you
But she said she was impressed the whole team because of how we worked the room and how we were talking to people engaging and how we were talking to my one
And selling my Emma, but that's what we're there for
Is to go down to make an impact and now we're seeing that the
repercussions in that again
So the results of that by now they're reaching back out to us
Ask him for the information and guys there's good things going and people want to be here
So when I'm gonna say that's right in the camera so whenever people go online and say nobody wants to be here at our towns dying and
We have all these issues we don't have any more issues in the other town has but I can tell you this people want to be here
And we want to be here and these guys things were doing here. It's shown them we wanted to be here
So it's not all them and good as my I want to turn it all way up when we're gonna keep going so I
Appreciate the channel and then to keep you in their efforts. They're done a great job. Yeah, I
I'll say the maids is an organization that's been around a long time and don't think it's ever been as effective for my Emma as it is today.
It could have been, but it wasn't utilizing the right way.
I took the same idea about the retail to a former maids director and her response was, we don't do that here.
Well, I took it to the channel and he said, let's do this.
And we haven't slowed down.
And good things are happening.
So when you have good people like this council, maids, our tribes, everybody working together, pull into the right direction and the same direction.
And looking for the same achievements and goals, they happen.
But it takes everybody.
And I think it's important to note too that even though we're talking about retail development and we have the last couple of times I've been here,
that does not mean we've stopped actively recruiting, manufacturing and light industry.
We're still doing all of those things.
We're looking for ways now to get more into the aeronautics industry and bringing some of those support services here to compliment some of the things that's going on,
saying growth in other areas around us, where those companies don't have to necessarily be in growth, but they provide parts and services to support what's happening in growth.
So we're still doing all of those things.
We're still trying to figure out how to get more houses built.
We've just added another element of what we're trying to do.
It's not easy, but it's what we need to do.
It's how we're going to grow.
So we're going to succeed.
So I appreciate the city setting representatives down the San Antonio.
We had two representatives from the Piora Trod that were there with us as well.
So we had quite the team in San Antonio and you will well represent it.
And I'll say to the Tyler was really on the housing development stuff while we were there.
He was meeting with some of those developers.
So he did get job done there too.
All right, guys. Thank you.
Thank you.
Five A claims list.
Most of you have proof.
Sorry.
These depth.
Double.
Jones.
Barnes.
Parker.
Five B.
Minutes from the Mark III.
2026.
Bring her meat.
One.
Double.
Jones.
Who?
Barnes.
Hey.
Five C.
Requests to transfer legacy homes from the police department property.
The surplus property.
She's.
So in your packet.
You have a list of firearms that we're wanting to transfer from our current inventory.
To surplus property.
The my increased requirement requested approval transfer
The following to permit and firearms.
Over to surplus property property and accordance with policy and asset management procedures.
The Police Department currently maintains several legacy firearms that no longer align with the department's
market and shooting platforms, qualification standards, or tactical equipment configurations.
Some of these weapons are 20 plus years old and are going to require some...
upkeep and some maintenance, and they cannot be converted to our current shooting platforms
without some significant investment into them, so we're requesting that we transfer these
into surplus property to use those funds for secondary source, which is my natural proposal.
So, we're going to start posting a solder.
So, my second proposal is what we're going to do with that, they will be traded for some
handguns.
I'll show you the proof.
Hi.
5D.
Authorization.
Trade-in.
Like the bar arm.
Like the new duty distance.
So, we sent out a proposal.
We got two responses back.
One from GT distributors, which is a nationwide distributor.
And also from H&H shooting sports.
H&H shooting sports is the only agency that would actually work with us, because
some ATF issues on some restricted firearm.
They actually worked with us through the process of getting the paperwork from ATF so that
we can actually transfer those firearms over.
And they did give us a confirmed trade-in value-quote dated January 28th.
So in your packet, you have the list of firearms that we want to transfer, which are also the ones
that we just approved to transfer over to surplus.
We want to, with this transfer, there are no longer consistent with our current department shooting
platforms like I discussed.
I would like to request authorization to trade these to H&H shooting sports and purchase
7Glock 45 Gen 5 Pistols and 7A.
Red.sites for a total price of $5,439.
The trade-in credit would be $3,800.
The remaining balance would come from the cell of our motorcycles in the city's surplus cell several
months back.
Currently I have zero handguns because of the two new hires.
So when we're another, we need to purchase some handguns.
Did you just buy a new gun?
No.
Three years.
Three years ago.
Okay.
So I mean, originally we go five years with one gun.
Yeah.
That's why.
So these are the next iteration of those firearms.
So we are moving up with these seven that I want to purchase.
So did you say we have two officers without anger?
No.
They got the last two.
Okay.
So when I have an officer that is retiring at the end of the month.
So I will have no surplus firearms if we have an instance.
If we have to take firearms from somebody and issue them a different one.
So that's another reason why we were asking them before with us.
But we're going to do without rifles, though, too.
So I still have rifles that are consistent with our shooting platform.
The ones that we are trading in are ones that they still have the carry hand
on.
I can't put red dots on them.
I can't put optics on them.
Do any sort.
They're not the M4 frames and off-clap.
I think I have six that we keep in the armory and each officer qualifies in certain rifles so that they, when they go to pull a rifle, they're pulling the same rifle.
We don't have a right enough for each officer.
That's in my budget.
Tyler and I have to talk about later.
Motion to prove.
Second.
Don't pull.
Don't buy burns.
All right.
He says.
And five E authorization to enter into an agreement with Lexipole for policy review update and ongoing maintenance.
Funding to be provided for the, oh, from the opioid abatement settlement funds.
So currently the city has an agreement, a contractual agreement with Lexipole for right services.
This is an addendum to those services in order for Lexipole to provide us with policy support.
The city has received the opioid abatement settlement funds and as we have learned, it's difficult to spend that funding.
However, through some research that I've done under appendix B exhibit E schedule B schedule B.
Our section B paragraph 11 training and development procedures for government staff to appropriately interact and provide social and other services to individuals with opioid use disorder, including reducing the stigma on effective treatment.
Lexipole services directly satisfy this under this proposal.
The city will expand its current contractive services to include Lexipole's policy manual and daily training buildings with services.
Comprehensive review and modernization of all Miami police department policies.
Reviewing policies right now.
The most recent update is 2014.
We're now in 2026.
So there needs to be a policy update.
By using Lexipole, they actually are legally vetted based on federal state and case law.
And consistently review that and update that every time something changes.
And that's part of our contractual agreement with them.
Integrated policy based training for officers.
So they will send Bolton's out and then I can have the officers test on the changes in the policy.
And then update it.
Access to opioid related policy modules, including Naxolone up, knocks alone updates.
And treatment first response standards.
Support for development of new policies, including our mental health co-responder.
We need a policy for that.
They're going to work with us to develop that policy also, which is paid for off of the opioid abatement grant that we received.
So these two kind of work together with each other.
The first year cost is 20,465 dollars.
Annual renewal cost is $18,335.
This will come out of the opioid abatement settlement fund and not out of general operating funds.
That's good.
five.
Thank you.
contract with Trent and Tanner.
for the route 66.
hair respectful in the amount of $500.
This is a contract for an entertainer for Friday night of Heritage Fest.
Who's to approve?
Second.
EastF.
Farms.
Jones.
Circle.
five.
G.
Bobby.
dig on you.
Go on you.
For the route 66.
Heritage Festival in the amount of $2,000.
Those two approve.
Second.
five.
Farms.
Jones.
five.
H contract with Jake Taylor.
For the route 66.
Heritage Festival in the amount of $1,750.
Most two approve.
five.
EastF.
What?
Jones.
Farms.
Five.
I.
contract with Chris Lane.
for the route 66.
Heritage Festival in the amount of $60,000.
Scheduled.
Jones.
Farms.
Circle.
Parker.
Thank you.
Appreciate you.
I'm six.
We're.
The eight.
Aren't the fairle men?
Let's go.
Business.
I'm in the school.
I'm a.
staff and staff report.
Council.
Community.
The.
is introduced.
L.
No, I think part of the requirement for their class is to attend at least one city council meeting do two city
I have to do something else because this
We'll sign your paper
No, we appreciate you guys, but in that time because I know it does take a lot of time to do that and did you guys just go to the capital?
How was that
That's what I'm talking about
I'm trying to all the way to the top of that dome.
There's like seven hundred, yeah, I did.
There's like 700 steps.
There's a little water.
Well, don't you carry a bottle of water?
And then you get to the top and you walk out.
And the wind was like a hundred miles an hour, almost blew us all out.
I don't know.
They actually make you sign a waiver, don't they?
Yeah, they make you sign a waiver.
Yeah, you have to sign a waiver.
I'm telling you, if you say 700 steps, it's within 10.
That's cool.
I would have looked at your pictures when you got down.
We had something that made it halfway and stopped.
Have you ever been up a pack loop?
I don't just want us to.
We got to tell this hop and somebody said, there's an elevator to get down, right?
I don't really.
Yeah.
I'm not sure I would even try.
There's a coffee shop down on the bottom.
That's probably right away.
Anybody else, anything?
City manager communications.
No, sir.
All right.
Number 10.
This means we're not going to be continuing from council chambers.
We're going to meet in the staff rooms.
Perfect.
I think executive session.